 var questions = [{
 	"question": "BYOD STANDS FOR?",
 	"option1": "BINMALEY YOUTH ORGANIZATION DEVELOPMENT",
 	"option2": "BIBLICAL YOUNG OR DEFENCE",
 	"option3": "BRING YOUR OWN DEVICE",
 	"option4": "BRING YOUNG ORW DEVICES",
 	"answer":"3"

}, {
	"question": "HOW TO INSTALL CORDOVA?",
 	"option1": "$NPM INSTALL -G GORDOVA",
 	"option2": "$NPM INSTALL -G CORDOVA",
 	"option3": "$NPM INSTALL -G CRODOVA",
 	"option4": "$NPM INSTALL -G CORDOVA@LATEST",
 	"answer":"2"
}, {
	"question": "HOW TO INSTALL REACTJS?",
	"option1": "$ npm installest -j create-react-app",
	"option2": "$ npm installer -g codova-react-app",
	"option3": "$ npm installing -g create-reactjs-app",
	"option4": "$ npm install -g create-react-app",
	"answer": "4"

}, {
	"question": "HOW TO UPLOAD YOUR FILES N GITHUB?",
	"option1": "GIT PUSH",
	"option2": "GET PUSH",
	"option3": "GIET PUSH",
	"option4": "GITS PUSH",
	"answer": "1"

}, {
	"question": "a free, open source framework for building cross-platform native applications using HTML5",
	"option1": "APACHE FOUNDATION",
	"option2": "APACHE CORDOVA ",
	"option3": "APACHE APPS",
	"option4": "APACHE FRAMEWORK7",
	"answer": "2"
}, {
	"question": "HOW TO RUN YOUR REACTJS IN CMD?",
	"option1": "$NPM RUN",
	"option2": "$NPM GO",
	"option3": "$NPM BUIILD",
	"option4": "$NPM START",
	"answer": "4"
}, {
	"question": "how",
	"option1": "russer westbrook",
	"option2": "kobe",
	"option3": "jordan",
	"option4": "durant",
	"answer": "1"
}, {
	"question": "who is the ccurrent president of the Philippines?",
	"option1": "noynoy aquino",
	"option2": "manuel roxas",
	"option3": "emilio aguinaldo",
	"option4": "rodrigo duterte",
	"answer": "4"
}, {
	"question": "what is year today ?",
	"option1": "2020",
	"option2": "2018",
	"option3": "2017",
	"option4": "1",
	"answer": "3"
}, {
	"question": "anu say mo??",
	"option1": "blog",
	"option2": "web",
	"option3": "idk",
	"option4": "were",
	"answer": "1"
}];


